http://www.bratney.com/privacy/

Privacy
This privacy statement has been created to protect the privacy of Bratney Companies online visitors. We collect no personally identifiable information through this website unless you voluntarily supply it. We define personally identifiable information as information that can uniquely identify an individual person.
Bratney Companies may use technology to obtain non-personal information from online visitors in order to improve the online experience, such as tracking the total number of visitors to areas of our website. Bratney Companies only gathers personally identifiable data when voluntarily submitted by a visitor. For example, personally identifiable information may be requested by Bratney Companies to respond to a request for more information about a product or service.
It is Bratney Companies’ policy to use personally identifiable information for Bratney Companies internal business purposes only. This information will not be shared or sold to third parties.
Bratney Companies privacy policy may be updated from time to time without notice, but will be posted on this page. Changes will not be applied retroactively.
Join Our Mailing List
Receive the latest news, product launches, case studies and more, delivered to your inbox.
First Name:
Email Address:
CASE STUDY: pOPCORN PLANT
Preferred Popcorn discusses their new popcorn conditioning and packaging facility, its technology and automation, and why they trusted Bratney Companies with the entire project.
Our Locations
Des Moines, Iowa
Boise, Idaho
Buenos Aires, Argentina
West Sacramento, California
Fargo, North Dakota
Connect With Us
News
Join Us at Pack Expo 2019!
Bratney Companies Integrates Critical Links In The Food Chain
View all Posts
© 2020 Bratney Companies
Privacy    |    Terms & Conditions    |    Patents    |    Sitemap    |
design & development by GLOBAL REACH
© 2020 Bratney Companies. All rights reserved.
